Online Converter

[Home](https://www.onlineconverter.com/) > [Privacy Policy](https://www.onlineconverter.com/privacy)

Privacy Policy
==============

OnlineConverter.com is committed to safeguarding the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand what we do. We ensure that we meet our responsibilities under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). and we will only ever use your data as this Privacy Policy describes.

1. Online Privacy Practices
    ------------------------
    
    OnlineConverter.com protects the privacy of your personal information on our websites using the same standards and care that we utilize for all OnlineConverter.com communications and transactions.
    
    OnlineConverter.com does not automatically collect personal information from visitors to our websites. However, we may automatically collect and store a little certain data from all website visitors, for example, the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of computers and the date and time the visitor accesses OnlineConverter.com websites. We use only these data to control files uploading, data processing, and file downloading, until such time as they expire (3 hours).
    
    OnlineConverter.com do not intentionally collect your name, your address, your email address and your telephone number. And we do not intentionally collect or store special categories of personal data, such as genetic data, health information, or religious information.
    
    Although we do not request or intentionally collect any special categories of personal data, we realize that you might store this kind of information via the files that you convert. If you ask us to convert or store any files containing special categories of personal data on our servers, located in the United States, we will only do so on your instructions as a data processor. You are the controller of this data and you must ensure that you have a legal basis to share this data with us.
    
    OnlineConverter.com may provide links from its websites to other vendors and third parties. Because OnlineConverter.com cannot guarantee how these third parties use or collect personally identifying information, you are encouraged to fully review the privacy statements of these other websites to determine whether or not your use of these websites comports with your desire to maintain the privacy of personally identifying information.
    
2. Use Of Cookies
    --------------
    
    OnlineConverter.com may use cookies to enhance the delivery of products, services, and information on OnlineConverter.com websites. A cookie is a small file that a website transfers to a visitor's computer hard drive to remind our website about the visitor when they return to our site. Cookies enable OnlineConverter.com to protect your personal information by ensuring that only your web browser may exchange information with OnlineConverter.com servers, and by automatically terminating an online session. Cookies also assist OnlineConverter.com in verifying your identity, and help us to understand how you use our websites. You can set your browser to notify you before accepting a cookie, so that you can decide whether to accept or reject the cookie.
    
3. Third Party Advertising
    -----------------------
    
    We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.
    
4. User Files
    ----------
    
    Your files and the content of those files belong to you, so it is important to know that as part of our commitment to privacy we will not share, sell or pass on your files to any third parties. When users upload files to be converted OnlineConverter.com stores those files on its servers until such time as those files have been converted to the new file format. Regardless of whether the conversion succeeded or failed, as soon as the conversion has been done OnlineConverter.com removes the original user files from its servers. The converted files remain in place on the servers for users to download, until such time as they expire (3 hours), at which point they are deleted, or in the case of a subscribed user until such time as that user deletes those files. Files stored for download are only accessible by OnlineConverter.com and through the clickable link generated for download.
    
5. Contact
    -------
    
    If you have questions, concerns, or if you desire additional information concerning the OnlineConverter.com Privacy Policy, please contact OnlineConverter.com.
    
    This Privacy Policy replaces all prior Privacy Policies issued by OnlineConverter.com. We reserve the right to modify our Privacy Policy at any time.

[Home](https://www.onlineconverter.com/) | [About](https://www.onlineconverter.com/about) | [Terms](https://www.onlineconverter.com/terms) | [Privacy](https://www.onlineconverter.com/privacy) | [Support](https://www.onlineconverter.com/support) | © 2024 OnlineConverter.com, All Rights Reserved.
